(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-16T21:16:59.634614",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
輪堂千速生誕祭2026 FlatOut SummerteS 重大告知あり
[Rindo Chihaya Birthday Celebration 2026: FlatOut SummerteS - Major Announcement Included]
みんな、ちはやー！
Hey everyone, Chihaya here!
生誕祭2026に来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you for coming to my Birthday Fest 2026!
盛り上がる準備できてるかー！
Are you ready to get hyped up?!
ぶち上げていくぞーー！
Let's blow the roof off!
でも、ちょっと今から急いでライブ会場にみんなを連れて行かなきゃなんないから、
But I've got to rush and take everyone to the concert venue right now,
一緒に行ってくれるか？
so will you come along with me?
行くぞー！
Here we go!
熱くなった銀のメタリックハート
My silver, metallic heart has heated up
導火線に火をつけてあげる
I'll light the fuse for you
不思議なほどハイな気分さ
I'm feeling strangely high
砂埃を巻き上げて行こう
Let's kick up the dust and go
悲鳴をまじらせ暴走する鼓動
Mingled with screams, my racing heartbeat
目の前にはミサイルの雨
Ahead of us is a shower of missiles
アドレナリンずっと流して
With adrenaline constantly flowing
僕の方がオーバーヒートしそう
Feels like I'm the one about to overheat
爆発して灰になっても
Even if I explode and turn to ash
このままだと笑ってるね きっと
I'm sure I'll still be laughing just like this
街を追い越して この世の果てまで
Overtaking the town, all the way to the ends of the earth
ぶっ飛ばして心中しよう さぁ手を伸ばして
Let's speed away and go out together, come on, reach out your hand!
地平線に届くように
So that we reach the horizon
限界まで振り切ってくれ
Redline it all the way to the limit!
Woh! Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
最高のフィナーレを! Yeah!
Towards the ultimate finale! Yeah!
もう数えるくらいで僕らは消え失せて
In just a few counts, we'll vanish away
真っ暗な朝が来るね
And a pitch-black morning will arrive
お気に入りの服に さぁ着替えたなら
Once you change into your favorite clothes,
駆け出して!
Dash out!
あきれるほど声をあげて
Cry out so loud it's absurd
大気圏を突破しようぜ
Let's break through the atmosphere!
Woh! Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
鋼の翼で
On wings of steel,
駆けぬけてよ 時間切れまで
Race on through until time runs out
生まれつきのスピード狂なのさ
'Cause I'm a born speed freak!
Woh! Clash! Into the rolling morning
Flash! I'm in the coolest driver's high
来世でまた会おう Yeah!
See you in the next life! Yeah!
広い宇宙の 数ある一つ
In this vast universe, one of many,
青い地球の 広い世界で
in the wide world of our blue Earth,
小さな恋の 思いは届く
these feelings of a small love will reach
小さな島の あなたのもとへ
to you on that little island.
あなたと出会い 時は流れる
Since meeting you, time has flowed by,
思いを込めた 手紙もふえる
and letters filled with feelings keep growing.
いつしか二人 互いに響く
Before we knew it, we resonated with each other,
時に激しく 時に切なく
at times intensely, at times heartbreakingly.
響くは遠く 遥か彼方へ
Echoing far away, to the distant beyond,
やさしい歌は 世界を変える
a gentle song changes the world.
ほら あなたにとって大事な人ほど
See? The more important someone is to you,
すぐそばにいるの
the closer they are by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ届いて欲しい
I just want it to reach you and you alone.
響け恋の歌
Ring out, song of love.
ほら...
Look...
響け恋の歌
Ring out, song of love.
あなたは気づく 二人は歩く
You notice, and the two of us walk,
暗い道でも 日々照らす月
even on dark roads, lit by the moon day after day.
握りしめた手 離すことなく
Never letting go of the hand held tight,
思いは強く 永遠誓う
our feelings grow stronger, swearing eternity.
永遠の淵 きっと僕は言う
At the brink of eternity, I'm sure I'll say,
思い変わらず 同じ言葉を
with unchanging feelings, the very same words.
それでも足りず 涙にかわり
Still not enough, turning into tears,
喜びになり
turning into joy,
言葉にできず ただ抱きしめる
unable to put it into words, I just hold you close,
ただ抱きしめる
I just hold you close.
ほら あなたにとって大事な人ほど
See? The more important someone is to you,
すぐそばにいるの
the closer they are by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ届いて欲しい
I just want it to reach you and you alone.
響け恋の歌
Ring out, song of love.
ほら...
Look...
響け恋の歌
Ring out, song of love.
夢ならば覚めないで
If this is a dream, don't wake me up.
あなたと過ごした時 永遠の星となる
The time spent with you becomes an eternal star.
ほら あなたにとって大事な人ほど
See? The more important someone is to you,
すぐそばにいるの
the closer they are by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ届いて欲しい
I just want it to reach you and you alone.
響け恋の歌
Ring out, song of love.
ほら あなたにとって大事な人ほど
See? The more important someone is to you,
すぐそばにいるの
the closer they are by your side.
ただ あなたにだけ届いて欲しい
I just want it to reach you and you alone.
響け恋の歌
Ring out, song of love.
ほら...
Look...
響け恋の歌
Ring out, song of love!
はーい！
Alright!
というわけで、
And so,
皆さん、輪堂千速生誕祭にお越しくださり、
everyone, thank you so much for coming
ありがとうございますー！
to the Rindo Chihaya Birthday Festival!
聞こえていますでしょうかー！
Can you all hear me?!
挨拶します！
Time for my intro greeting!
位置について、レッツゴー！
On your marks, let's go!
やばい、フラフラだ。
Oh gosh, I'm dizzy.
ぶっちぎりの運転担当、輪堂千速です！
In charge of driving full throttle, I'm Rindo Chihaya!
こんちはー！
Hello, everyone!
ということで、始まりました！
And with that, it has begun!
初めての3D生誕ライブー！
My very first 3D Birthday Live!
いっぱい盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's get super hyped up together!
配信のハッシュタグは右上、
The stream hashtag is in the top right,
あ、あ、これ、あ、右上、こちらになります。
ah, ah, here—ah, in the top right right here.
ハッシュタグ #輪堂千速生誕祭2026 になるので、
It's #輪堂千速生誕祭2026,
たくさんポストしていただけるととっても嬉しいです！
so I'd be super happy if you post a ton with it!
ちゃんと見ますからねー！
I'll definitely be checking them!
是非あの、トレンド1位とかなれたりしたら嬉しいなーなんて思うので、
I'd really love it if we could reach number one on trending or something,
いっぱいスクショとかね、貼ってポスト...
so please post lots of screenshots and...
...出してもらえると嬉しいです！
...I'd be really happy if you do!
うわ、こんにちは！いっぱいありがとうー！
Whoa, hello! Thank you so much for all the comments!
ということでね 一旦ちょっと2曲歌わせていただいたので
So now that I've sung two songs,
振り返っていこうかなと思うんですが
I thought we could look back on them...
まずは1曲目！
First off, the first song!
「Driver's High」を 海沿いをフグタロウでドライブしながら歌わせていただきました！
I got to sing "Driver's High" while driving along the coast in Fugutaro!
どうでしたでしょうか？
How did you like it?
デビューのね 一番最初にラルクの曲を歌ってて
Right at my debut, the very first song I sang was by L'Arc~en~Ciel,
で この「Driver's High」をいつか歌ってほしいってすごい言われていたので
and so many people told me they wanted to hear me sing "Driver's High" someday,
絶対に生誕で歌おうと思って 1曲目に選びました！
so I decided I'd definitely sing it for my birthday, and picked it as the opening track!
いや あの…まあ あそこCOVERの私有地なので
Well, um... you see, that was COVER's private property,
色々諸々ひっくるめて オッケーです！
so taking all things into account, it's totally okay!
大丈夫！大丈夫！きっと大丈夫！
It's fine! It's fine! Surely it's fine!
そして2曲目は「小さな恋のうた」でした！どうでしたか？！
And the second song was "Chiisana Koi no Uta"! How was that?!
そう！これ！
That's right! This!
千速が弾いてましたよー！
Chihaya was actually playing it!
いや あの ご存知の方も多いかなと思いますがね
Well, I think many of you already know,
エレキを購入しまして練習していたんですが
but I bought an electric guitar and have been practicing,
あの 弾かせていただきました！
and I got to perform it for you!
やっぱりなんか エレキで初めて挑戦するのって
After all, when it comes to taking on your very first guitar song,
なんか「小さな恋のうた」だよなってイメージがあって この曲を選んだんですけど
I've always felt "Chiisana Koi no Uta" is the classic choice, which is why I chose it, but...
すんげー難しい！
It was crazy hard!
すんげー難しかったんですけど
It was super difficult, but...
でもね 生誕ライブでかっこいいところ見せたかったので
But I really wanted to show you my cool side in this birthday live,
いっぱい いっぱい いっぱい練習して…
so I practiced over and over and over again...
弾けてたよね？なんとか！
I managed to play it, right? Somehow!
弾けてたと思います！
I think I pulled it off!
なのでね いっぱいあの 後でアーカイブとかも見直して聴いてくれると嬉しいです！
So I'd be really happy if you check out the archive later and listen to it again!
ということで そしてね
And with that... also,
お気づきの方もいますが 「小さな恋のうた」最初は体育館だったんですけど
as some of you may have noticed, "Chiisana Koi no Uta" started out in a gymnasium,
外に出てきましたよー！
but we came outside!
やっぱ夏といえば外！海！山！自然！
Summer is all about the outdoors! The ocean! Mountains! Nature!
そして夏の音楽といえばフェス！
And when it comes to summer music, it's festivals!
をイメージして 夏フェス会場になっております！
With that in mind, we've set up a full summer festival stage!
後ろにはね 海もあって もう最高のロケーションで
Behind us we have the ocean, making it the absolute best location,
今日はフェスを開催していければなと思っております！
and I hope we can keep rocking this festival today!
こんなにね 広いので あっちに行ったり…
It's so spacious, so I can go over there...
あ 予定にない動きをしてすいません 本当に
Ah, sorry for moving around unscripted, really!
こっちに行ったりしていこうと思っています！
...and move around over here!
では まぁちょっとあんまり喋るとね あれなので 次の曲行こうと思うので
Well, if I talk too much it'll eat up time, so let's head into the next song.
ちょっと準備するのでギターとマイク置いてきます
I'll go set down my guitar and mic to get ready.
ちょっと待っててね 行ってきます！
Wait just a bit, be right back!
はい ということで
Alright, and so...
はい 来ました来ました！
Yes, here I am, back again!
ということで ここからはですね ゲストブロックになります！
So starting now, it's time for the guest block!
ので この後もいっぱい楽しんでいってください！
So please keep having a blast from here on!
盛り上がっていくぞー！
Let's get hyped!
GO!!! / 作詞: KOHSHI 作曲: TAKE
[Song: GO!!! / Lyrics: KOHSHI / Composition: TAKE]
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers, aiming high
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, heedless of how we look
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers, just as we believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here, Right now (BANG!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Right here, Right now (BANG!) Blast away like a bullet line drive!
Right here, Right now (BURN!) ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
Right here, Right now (BURN!) Slash right through and get the fire!
Right here, Right now (BANG!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Right here, Right now (BANG!) Blast away like a bullet line drive!
Right here, Right now (BURN!)
険しい修羅の道の中 他人の地図を広げて何処へ行く?
On this harsh, perilous road, spreading out someone else's map, where are you going?
極彩色のカラスが それを奪い取って破り捨てた
A multicolored crow snatched it away and tore it to shreds
さぁ 心の目見開いて しかと真実を見極めろ! (Yeah!)
Come on, open the eyes of your heart and clearly see the truth! (Yeah!)
失うモノなんてないさ いざ参ろう!
We've got nothing to lose, so let's go!
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers, aiming high
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, heedless of how we look
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers, just as we believe
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here, Right now (BANG!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Right here, Right now (BANG!) Blast away like a bullet line drive!
Right here, Right now (BURN!)
音を立てず忍び寄る影が いつも僕らを惑わせる
Shadows creeping up without a sound always try to lead us astray
有言実行 大きな風が うねりを上げて吹き荒れる
Words into action, a mighty wind swells up and storms fiercely
かざした鋭い刀で 己の未来切り開け! (Yeah!)
With the sharp blade held high, carve out your own future! (Yeah!)
保証なんて どこにも無いさ なぁ そうだろ!?
There are no guarantees anywhere, hey, isn't that right?!
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers, aiming high
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, heedless of how we look
Fighting Dreamers 信じるが…
Fighting Dreamers, as we believe...
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) Fire it off like a bullet liner!
Right here, Right now (Burn!) ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
Right here, Right now (Burn!) Slicing right through, get the fire!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) Fire it off like a bullet liner!
Right here, Right now (Burn!) ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
Right here, Right now (Burn!) Slicing right through, get the fire!
We are Fighting Dreamers この仲間達と
We are Fighting Dreamers, together with these comrades,
Fighting Dreamers 全てを巻き込み
Fighting Dreamers, pulling everything along with us,
Fighting Dreamers 志高く
Fighting Dreamers, aiming high,
Oli Oli Oli Oh-!
We are Fighting Dreamers 高みを目指して
We are Fighting Dreamers, aiming for the top,
Fighting Dreamers なりふり構わず
Fighting Dreamers, without caring how it looks,
Fighting Dreamers 信じるがままに
Fighting Dreamers, staying true to what we believe,
Oli Oli Oli Oh-! Just go my way!
Don't forget your first impulse ever (Go my way!)
Let's keep your adventurous ever (Go my way!)
Don't forget your first impulse ever
Let's keep your adventurous ever
Go! Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Go! Right here, Right now (Bang!) Fire it off like a bullet liner!
Right here, Right now (Burn!) ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
Right here, Right now (Burn!) Slicing right through, get the fire!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) ぶっ放せ Like a 弾丸ライナー!
Right here, Right now (Bang!) Fire it off like a bullet liner!
Right here, Right now (Burn!) ぶった斬ってくぜ Get the fire!
Right here, Right now (Burn!) Slicing right through, get the fire!
カルマ
作詞・作曲: 藤原基央
[Karma]
[Lyrics & Music: Motoo Fujiwara]
ガラス玉ひとつ 落とされた 追いかけてもうひとつ落っこちた
A single glass marble was dropped; chasing after it, another one tumbled down.
ひとつ分の陽だまりに ひとつだけ残ってる
In a patch of sunlight meant for one, only one remains.
心臓が始まった時 嫌でも人は場所を取る
From the moment a heart starts beating, like it or not, a person takes up space.
奪われない様に 守り続けてる
Constantly protecting it so it won't be stolen away.
汚さずに保ってきた 手でも汚れて見えた
Even the hands kept untainted began to look dirty.
記憶を疑う前に 記憶に疑われてる
Before I could doubt my memories, I was being doubted by them.
必ず僕らは出会うだろう
Surely, we are destined to meet,
同じ鼓動の音を目印にして
guided by the sound of the very same heartbeat.
ここに居るよ いつだって呼んでるから
I am right here; because I'm always calling out to you.
くたびれた理由が 重なって揺れる時 生まれた意味を知る
When worn-out reasons overlap and sway, we come to understand the meaning of being born.
存在が続く限り 仕方ないから場所を取る
As long as our existence continues, we have no choice but to take up space.
ひとつ分の陽だまりに ふたつはちょっと入れない
In a patch of sunlight meant for one, two just cannot fit.
ガラス玉ひとつ 落とされた 落ちた時 何か弾き出した
A single glass marble was dropped; when it fell, it pushed something out.
奪い取った場所で 光を浴びた
Basking in the light at the spot stolen away.
数えた足跡など 気付けば数字でしかない
The footprints I counted, when realized, are nothing more than numbers.
知らなきゃいけない事は どうやら1と0の間
What we truly need to know lies somewhere between 1 and 0.
初めて僕らは出会うだろう
For the very first time, we will meet,
同じ悲鳴の旗を目印にして
guided by the flag of our matching screams.
忘れないで いつだって呼んでるから
Don't forget; because I'm always calling out to you.
重なった理由を ふたりで埋める時 約束が交わされる
When the two of us bury those overlapping reasons, a promise is exchanged.
鏡なんだ 僕ら互いに
We are mirrors to one another,
それぞれのカルマを映すための
meant to reflect each of our respective karmas.
汚れた手と手で触り合って 形が解る
Touching with our stained hands, we understand each other's form.
ここに居るよ 確かに触れるよ
I am right here; you can truly touch me.
ひとり分の陽だまりに 僕らはいる
In a patch of sunlight meant for one, here we are.
忘れないで いつだって呼んでるから
Don't forget; because I'm always calling out to you,
同じガラス玉の内側のほうから
from inside the very same glass marble.
そうさ 必ず僕らは出会うだろう
That's right, we are surely destined to meet.
沈めた理由に十字架を立てる時 約束は果たされる
When we erect a cross upon the sunken reasons, the promise will be fulfilled.
僕らは ひとつになる
We will become one.
Woah...
今日も君は 信じること
Today, were you able to wake up
忘れずに目覚められていますか？
without forgetting what you believe in?
時が経つと 自分さえも信じれなくなる時代のようです
As time passes, it seems we live in an era where we can't even believe in ourselves.
自分では気付かないのが この症状の特徴で
The characteristic of this symptom is that you don't even realize it yourself,
唯一ある予防法…は
and the only preventive measure... is:
「自分にウソだけゃつかない事」
"Never lie to yourself."
忘れてたまるもんかよ！！
As if I'd ever forget!!
僕がボクじゃなくなったら
If I'm no longer myself,
たとえ生きてたって 生きてる意味すら見つからんだろ
even if I were alive, I wouldn't even find a reason to live!
声にならない叫びは 僕が声を枯らして
For these soundless screams, I'll scream until my voice gives out,
叫んで歌って
screaming and singing,
伝わるまでわめいて
shouting until it gets through,
届くまで止めない！！
and I won't stop until it reaches you!!
今日も地球は 回り続ける
Today too, the world keeps on spinning,
誰が泣いても 怒っても止まらず
never stopping whether someone cries or gets angry.
ためしに僕が…
Just to test it, even if I...
風邪をひいても もちろん止まる事なんてねーわ！！
catch a cold, of course it's not gonna stop!!
人生も同じように 止まる事はなく進むし
Life moves forward just the same without ever stopping,
だから そうさ今日も人は お手手のシワとシワをあわせんの！！
so yeah, people put the wrinkles of their hands together in prayer today too!!
終わらせちまう事なんか 誰にだってできんだろ？！
Anyone can easily just end it, right?!
たとえ終わっちまったって 次のスタートすぐきれんだろ？！
Even if it came to an end, you can immediately make the next start, right?!
今キミが思うキセキも 底上げさせてしまえば
If you elevate the standard of what you now consider a miracle,
もうその時点でそのキセキは 君にとっちゃ必然のお仲間さ！！
at that point, that miracle becomes your inevitable companion!!
WOW！！
Woah!!
ダン ダンダ ダン ダン ダン...
Dan, dan da dan, dan, dan...
Without you...
WOW！ 何回ダメダメと言われようが
Woah! No matter how many times they tell me "No way,"
実際問題そんなん関係なくて
when it comes down to it, none of that matters!
今自分自身 必要なものたくわえてそろえとけよ！！
Right now, stock up and prepare everything you yourself need!!
なぁそうだろ？！ まだまだ！！ 時間はまだあんぞ！！
Hey, isn't that right?! Not yet, not yet!! There's still time!!
先見の明 今は研ぎ澄まして
Sharpen your foresight right now!
主人公は一人だけ！！ 自分の物語のはじまり！！
There is only one protagonist!! This is the beginning of your own story!!
もうすぐ時計は6時
Soon the clock will strike six,
もうそこに一番星
and the first evening star is already right there.
影を踏んで 夜に紛れたくなる帰り道
Stepping on shadows, on the way home wanting to melt into the night.
どんなに探してみても 一つしかない星
No matter how hard I search, there's only one single star.
何億光年 離れたところから
From hundreds of millions of light-years away...
...から あんなに輝く
...from so far away, you shine so bright.
いいな 君は みんなから愛されて
Must be nice, you're loved by everyone.
「いいや 僕はずっと一人きりさ」
"No way, I've always been all alone."
君と集まって星座になれたら
If you and I could come together and form a constellation,
星降る夜 一瞬の願い事
on a night of shooting stars, a split-second wish...
きらめいて ゆらめいて 震えてるシグナル
Glittering, flickering, trembling signals.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If you and I could come together and form a constellation,
空見上げて 指を差されるような
people would look up at the sky and point at us.
繋いだ線 解かないで
Don't untie the line connecting us,
僕がどんなに眩しくても
no matter how dazzling I might be.
もうすぐ時計は8時
Soon the clock will strike eight,
夜空に満天の星
the night sky full of stars.
何億光年 離れたところには もうないかもしれない
Hundreds of millions of light-years away, they might not even be there anymore.
月が綺麗で 泣きそうになるのは
The reason the beautiful moon brings me to tears
いつの日にか 別れが来るから
is because someday, a farewell will come.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If you and I could come together and form a constellation...
彗星みたい 流れるひとりごと
A monologue drifting like a comet,
消えていく残像は 真夜中のプリズム
the fading afterimage is a midnight prism.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If you and I could come together and form a constellation,
切なる願い 誰かに届いたら
if my earnest wish could reach someone,
変われるかな 夜のふちを
could I change? Even someone like me,
なぞるような こんな僕でも
who merely traces the edges of the night.
はるか彼方 僕らは出会ってしまった
Far away in the distance, we happened to meet.
カルマだから 何度も出会ってしまうよ
Because it's karma, we'll keep meeting again and again,
雲の隙間で
through the gaps in the clouds.
君と集まって星座になれたら
If you and I could come together and form a constellation,
夜を広げて 描こう絵空事
let's spread out the night and paint our daydreams.
暗闇を照らすような 満月じゃなくても
Even if we're not a full moon lighting up the dark,
だから集まって星座になりたい
that's why I want to gather and become a constellation,
色とりどりの光 放つような
casting a brilliance of colorful light.
繋いだ線 解かないよ
I won't untie the line connecting us,
君がどんなに眩しくても
no matter how dazzling you might be.
はい！ということでね！FLOW GLOWでー！
All right! So there you have it! From FLOW GLOW—!
イエーイ！
Yay!
聴いてくれてありがとう！
Thank you so much for listening!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
大丈夫？ / 息整えてね
Are you guys okay? / Catch your breath!
あの、FGでね、ずっとバンドがやりたいと思ってたので、
So, I've always wanted to do a band with FG,
今日はちょっとエアバンドなんですけどね、みんなで『星座になれたら』を披露させていただきました！
so even though we're an air band today, we performed "If I Could Be a Constellation" for you all!
楽しかったー！
That was so fun!
じゃあ1回、自己紹介しとくか！
All right, let's do some quick introductions!
オッケー！
Okay!
じゃあ、りっちゃんから！いつもの順番でお願いします！
Let's start with Ri-chan! Usual order, please!
はーい！私のもとにおいでよ！In the House!
Okay! Come over to me! In the House!
FLOW GLOWの、ギ... ギターボーカルじゃない、ベース担当！響咲リオナです！
In FLOW GLOW, I'm... not guitar & vocal, but on bass! I'm Isaki Riona!
いいね！弾く姿も格好良いよ、リオナ！
Nice! You look super cool playing the bass, Riona!
千早ちゃん、お誕生日おめでとー！
Chihaya-chan, happy birthday!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
そしてー？
And next?
にこたんが来たー！hololive DEV_IS、FLOW GLOWの...
Niko-tan is here! From hololive DEV_IS, FLOW GLOW's...
なんだっけあれ？キーボード！キーボード担当、虎金妃笑虎、にこたんだよー！
What was it again? Keyboard! On keyboard, I'm Koganei Niko, Niko-tan!
にこたん、ありがとうー！
Thank you, Niko-tan!
そしてー？
And next?
はーい！寿司は酢飯まで愛してる、hololive DEV_IS、FLOW GLOWのドラム担当、水宮枢でーす！
Yes! Loving sushi right down to the vinegared rice! From hololive DEV_IS, FLOW GLOW's drummer, Mizumiya Su!
千早、お誕生日おめでとー！
Chihaya, happy birthday!
すーちゃん、ありがとうー！
Thank you, Su-chan!
そしてー？
And next?
あ、はーい！せーの、ヴィーヴィー！
Ah, okay! Ready, set, Vivi!
キラキラな きっ、キラら Viviでーす！
Sparkling and glittering, it's Vivi!
あ、忘れてた！Viviはギター担当！
Ah, I forgot! Vivi is on guitar!
ジャカジャカ... 足で弾いてたもんね。足で弾いてるよ。
*Strum strum*... You were playing with your feet, right? / Yeah, with my feet!
なるほどね。
I see.
ちは、お誕生日おめでとー！
Chiha, happy birthday!
ありがとー！嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy!
いやということで、みんな来てくれてありがとう！
Well then, thank you so much for coming, everyone!
え、なんかもお知らせがあるんじゃないの？ お？
Wait, don't you have another announcement? / Oh?
なんと、トレンド1位になったらしいです！
Turns out, we reached #1 on trending!
やったー！すごい！嬉しい！
Yay! Amazing! I'm so happy!
なんか今までね、ちはって2文字だから、
Until now, "Chiha" is only two characters,
あのトレンドに乗らねーのよ。
so it wouldn't trend.
ああ、なるほどね。そうそう。
Ah, I see. / Right, right.
だからなんか乗ったらいいなと思ってたんだけど、
So I was hoping it would trend,
こんなね、誕生日に嬉しいプレゼントをいただきまして、本当にありがとうございます。
and receiving such a wonderful birthday present makes me truly grateful.
ねえ、いっぱいツイートしてくれたんだ。ありがとー！
Everyone tweeted so much! Thank you!
おめでとー！
Congratulations!
はい、ということで「星座になれたら」を披露しましたけど、皆さんどうでしたか？
All right, we just performed "If I Could Be a Constellation," how was it, everyone?
楽しかった！ドラムを叩きたくなりました。
It was so fun! It made me want to play drums.
似合ってたよね、ドラムね。
Drums really suited you!
経験者なんだよね。そうなんだよ、実は。
You're actually experienced, right? / Yeah, actually.
だからいつかFGバンドをね...
So someday, an FG band...
絶対できる！結成したいの！
We can definitely do it! / I want to form one!
ちょっと今回はエアバンドだったので、にこたんにね、キーボードを担当していただいたんですけど、
This time it was an air band, and we had Nico-tan play keyboard,
あれもうね、すごかったでしょう。
but man, wasn't she incredible?
指さばきが！もうすごかった、本当に！
Her fingerwork! It was seriously amazing!
全身で弾いてたもんね。
You were playing with your whole body, right?
全身で弾いてくれてた。そういうことやね。
She played with her whole body. That's right.
全然いつでもやるよ、マジで。
I'd do it anytime, seriously.
いや、できひんできひん。一歩もフレッドにね...
No, no way. Not even one fret...
どこ弾いてんの！イェーイ！
Where were you even playing?! / Yay!
でもみんなで楽しー、でもちはもすごい楽しかったし、なんかみんなも楽しそうにしてくれてとっても嬉しかったです。
But everyone had fun—Chiha had a blast too, and seeing everyone have fun made me so happy.
いつか実現させましょう！
Let's make it a reality someday!
したい、したい！しよう、しよう！
I want to, I want to! / Let's do it, let's do it!
え、そんな時はみんな今回の楽器でいいんですか？
Wait, when that time comes, is everyone fine with their current instruments?
うん... え？ 聞こえんかったって。
Yeah... Huh? / What? You didn't hear?
違う楽器がやりたいって。
She says she wants to play a different instrument.
俺の楽器が... 歌うたう！
My instrument is... / I'll sing, sing!
歌ダメ！ダメ！まず喧嘩になっとる。
No singing! No! / They're already fighting!
え、にこたんはさ、やるとしたら何の楽器やりたい？
Nico-tan, if you were to play, what instrument would you want?
いや、だってもう出くくってるよね、もうね。ギター？
Well, pretty much everything's covered, right? Guitar?
今ギター、ギター、ドラム、ベースがいるんだけど...
Right now we have guitar, guitar, drums, and bass...
そしたらでもやっぱキーボードしかないんじゃない？
In that case, isn't keyboard the only one left?
バイオリン、バイオリン！これがあるやん！
Violin, violin! There's always this!
いや、ちょっと違う気がする。でもバイオリン入ってるバンドめっちゃかっこいいよ。
No, that feels a bit off. / But bands with violins are super cool!
打楽器はどう？トライアングルとか。
How about percussion? Like the triangle.
トライアングルとかカスタネットとか、タンバリンとか。
Triangle, castanets, tambourine...
全員でなんか打楽器バンド？
All of us as a percussion band?
打楽器バンド！Viviは本当にそれでいいのか？
A percussion band! / Vivi, are you really okay with that?
シンバル。全然違うタイミングでやるからやめろ、それは。
Cymbals. / You'd hit them at totally the wrong timing, so don't do that!
そういうのもやってみたい、楽しそう。
I'd like to try that too, it sounds fun!
FGの企画とかでやったりするのね。
We could do it for an FG project.
確かにね。やりましょう、やりましょう！
True! Let's do it, let's do it!
ということでね、今回はFGちゃんたちに来ていただきまして、
So, thank you to the FG girls for joining us today,
本当に今日はね、長い時間リハーサルから付き合ってもらって、本当にありがとう！
and really, thank you so much for sticking with me through the long rehearsals today!
おめでとー！
Happy birthday!
お礼は何でも、ちはが何でもします券を皆様に贈呈しますので。
As thanks, I will present everyone with a "Chiha Will Do Anything" coupon.
え！？マジで！？何でもって言ったな！？
Eh?! Seriously?! You said "anything"?!
1人1枚？1人1枚。やったー！
One per person? / One per person. / Yay!
取り消し？取り消し券出して！
Cancel it? / Issue a cancellation ticket!
取り消し券なんてないよ！
There's no cancellation ticket!
ちは、美味しいご飯ごちそうさまです！いいよー！
Chiha, thanks for the delicious meal! / Sure thing!
それはもう全員に奢らせていただきます。
I'll treat everyone to that, of course!
食べたいもの教えてください。今日もお弁当豪華だったしな。
Tell me what you want to eat. / Today's bento boxes were luxurious too!
お弁当めっちゃ豪華だった！奮発しました！よかった喜んでいただいて。
The bentos were super fancy! / I splurged on them! Glad you enjoyed them.
ありがとう！まだあるので持って帰ってください。
Thank you! / There are still extras, so please take some home.
はーい！ではね、そろそろ次の曲に行きたいと思います！
Okay! Now then, I'd like to move on to the next song!
おー！みんなも見ててくれるかな？
Oh! Will all of you keep watching?
バッチリ見てるよ！
You bet we will!
では、ライブ見てくれてるみんなもまだまだ盛り上がっていってくださいねー！
Everyone watching the stream, keep getting hyped up, okay?!
イェーイ！
Yay!
まだコメント欄は何でもって言ってる。
The chat is still talking about "anything."
まだ言ってる？まだまだだよ。
Still going on? / Still going!
早速帰ろうとしないで。
Don't try to leave right away!
リスナーさんたちには何でもしないですけど、FGちゃんたちには何でもしたい気持ちでいますよ。
I won't do anything for listeners, but I'm ready to do anything for FG!
もちろんそれぐらいの愛がありますから。
Of course, that's how much love I have for them.
気持ちだけじゃなくてね。
Not just in spirit, right?
ついてくるからみんな、はい。バイバーイ！ありがとねー！
They're following, okay everyone, bye-bye! Thank you!
俺も一緒に行こう。シュッシュッシュッシュッ...
I'll go with them. *Choo choo choo choo...*
打上花火
[Title: Uchiage Hanabi]
あの日見渡した渚を
I can still remember the shore we saw that day...
今も思い出すんだ
It still comes back to my mind.
砂の上に刻んだ言葉
The words we carved into the sand,
君の後ろ姿
and the sight of your back as you walked away.
寄り返す波が 足元を
The incoming waves wash over my feet...
...よぎり 何かをさらう
...crossing my feet, carrying something away.
夕凪の中
In the evening calm,
日暮れだけが通り過ぎて行く
twilight alone passes me by.
パッと光って咲いた 花火を見ていた
We watched the fireworks blooming in a flash of light,
きっとまだ 終わらない夏が
hoping this summer wasn't over yet,
曖昧な心を 解かして繋いだ
as it melted and bound our uncertain hearts.
この夜が 続いて欲しかった
I wanted this night to go on forever.
あと何度君と同じ花火を見られるかなって
Wondering how many more times I could watch the fireworks with you,
笑う顔に何ができるだろうか
what can I do for your smiling face?
傷つくこと 喜ぶこと 繰り返す波と情動
Getting hurt, feeling joy, repeating waves and emotions,
焦燥 最終列車の音
impatience, and the sound of the last train.
何度でも 言葉にして君を呼ぶよ
Again and again, I'll put it into words and call your name,
波間を選び もう一度
choosing the moments between waves, once more,
もう二度と悲しまずに 済むように
so that you'll never have to feel sad again.
ハッと息を呑めば 消えちゃいそうな光が
A light that seemed it would disappear if we gasped for breath,
きっとまだ 胸に住んでいた
surely still lived on within our hearts.
手を伸ばせば触れた あったかい未来は
The warm future we could touch if we reached out our hands,
密かに二人を見ていた
was secretly watching over the two of us.
パッと花火が (パッと花火が)
In a flash, fireworks (in a flash, fireworks)
夜に咲いた (夜に咲いた)
bloomed in the night (bloomed in the night,)
夜に咲いて (夜に咲いて)
静かに消えた (静かに消えた)
and quietly disappeared (and quietly disappeared.)
離さないで (離れないで)
Don't let go (don't leave me,)
もう少しだけ (もう少しだけ)
just a little longer (just a little longer,)
もう少しだけ このままで
just a little longer, stay like this.
あの日見渡した渚を
Looking back at the shore we gazed upon that day,
今も思い出すんだ
I still remember it even now:
砂の上に刻んだ言葉
the words carved into the sand,
君の後ろ姿
and the sight of your back as you walked away.
パッと光って咲いた 花火を見ていた
We watched the fireworks blooming in a flash of light,
きっとまだ 終わらない夏が
hoping this summer wasn't over yet,
曖昧な心を 解かして繋いだ
as it melted and bound our uncertain hearts.
この夜が 続いて欲しかった
I wanted this night to go on forever.
ラララ...
La la la...
ソラニン
[Song: Solanin]
思い違いは 空のかなた
Our misunderstandings drift beyond the sky.
さよならだけの 人生か
Is life nothing but a series of goodbyes?
ほんの少しの 未来は見えたのに
Even though I could catch a glimpse of the future...
見えたのに
...even though I saw it,
さよならなんだ
it's goodbye after all.
昔住んでた 小さな部屋は
The small room I used to live in
今は他人が住んでんだ
is occupied by someone else now.
君に言われた ひどい言葉も
The cruel words you said to me,
無駄な気がした 毎日も
and the days that felt meaningless too...
あの時こうしていれば
If only I had done things differently back then,
あの日に戻れれば
if only I could return to that day...
あの頃の僕には もう戻れないよ
I can no longer go back to who I was in those days.
たとえばゆるい幸せが
For example, if a gentle kind of happiness
だらっと続いたとする
had simply dragged on lazily,
きっと悪い種が芽を出して
surely bad seeds would sprout,
もう さよならなんだ
and it would already be goodbye.
寒い冬の冷えた缶コーヒー
A cold can of coffee in the freezing winter,
虹色の長いマフラー
and a long rainbow-colored scarf.
小走りで路地裏を抜けて
Jogging lightly through the back alleys,
思い出してみる
I try to remember.
たとえばゆるい幸せが
For example, if a gentle kind of happiness
だらっと続いたとする
had simply dragged on lazily,
きっと悪い種が芽を出して
surely bad seeds would sprout,
もう さよならなんだ
and it would already be goodbye.
なんだ
That's how it is,
how it is,
なんだ
how it is.
さよなら それもいいさ
Goodbye — that's fine too.
どこかで元気でやれよ
Be well somewhere out there.
さよなら 僕もどーにかやるさ
Goodbye — I'll manage somehow too.
さよなら そうするよ
Goodbye — yeah, I will.
はい、じゃあ…
All right then...
はい！ ということで
Yes! And with that,
「ソラニン」をお送りしました！
that was "Soranin"!
いかがだったでしょうかー？
How did you like it?
いや、あの、見覚えがある方もいらっしゃるのではない…
Well, some of you might even recognize this...
でしょうか？
right?
これ、まあ、初めて見る方もいらっしゃるかなと思うんですが、
Though there might be people seeing this for the first time,
あの、FGの3Dお披露目の時にも、
back during Flow Glow's 3D debut,
ギターの弾き語りをお披露目させていただいたんですけれども、
I performed singing with an acoustic guitar as well,
その時よりもレベルアップできていたでしょうか？
and was I able to level up since then?
初めて多分、最初の頃に練習したのが「ソラニン」で、
Probably the very first song I practiced was "Soranin,"
そこからずっと、ちゃんとできた姿をみんなに見せたかったので、この曲を選びました！
and since I've always wanted to show everyone how well I can play it now, I chose this song!
そしてですね、ギター、ちはの音だけじゃなくて、もう1本ソロとかベースがあったと思うんですが、
Also, along with my guitar, you probably noticed another guitar solo and bass line,
それはですね、ちはのギターの先生に一緒に弾いていただきました！
that was actually played together with my guitar teacher!
レッスン時にセッションしてたら、「え、めっちゃかっこよくね？」ってなって、
When we were jamming during a lesson, we were like, "Wait, isn't this super cool?"
「先生もよかったら一緒に弾いてくれませんか？」って言って、
So I asked, "Teacher, would you play along with me if you'd like?"
一緒にね、弾いていただきました。ありがとうございました！
and they played with me! Thank you so much!
ということでね、一旦ここまでの振り返りをしていこうかなと思いますよ！
So with that, let's take a look back at everything up to this point!
まずは、ゲストパートで1曲目がツボハチで…
First off, for the guest part, the first song with Tsubohachi was...
ファインディング・ドリーマー
...Finding Dreamer!
しました！どうですか？やっぱ1曲目はぶち上げていきたいなと思って、
That was it! How was it? I wanted to kick things off with a bang for the first song,
飛ばしてね、めっちゃ盛り上がる曲を選びました！
so I chose a super hype song to start things off with a blast!
先輩達のぶち上げがカッコよくて、ちはも「頑張るぞー」ってなったので、楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいです。
The senpais' high-energy vibes were so cool, and it fired me up to give it my all too! I hope you all enjoyed it.
そして、2曲目はトワ様と『Karma』を歌いました！
And for the second song, I sang "Karma" with Towa-sama!
やっぱトワ様の低音が大好きなので、
I absolutely love Towa-sama's deep, low notes,
ちょっと無理を言って原曲キーでね、すごい低い中、一緒に歌っていただきました！
so I asked a bit of an unreasonable request and had her sing in the original key, which is really low!
トワ様、ありがとうございます！めっちゃカッコよかったです！
Thank you so much, Towa-sama! It was super cool!
そして、3曲目がルイ先輩と『じぶんROCK』！
And then the third song was "Jibun ROCK" with Lui-senpai!
いや、カッコよすぎない？やっぱルイ先輩カッコよすぎない？ヤバいんですけど！
Seriously, wasn't that way too cool? Lui-senpai was just ridiculously awesome, it was insane!
本当にルイ先輩のカッコいい、ちょっとがなりの効いた、エッジの効いた声で歌いたいなと思ってこの曲を選びました。
I really wanted to sing with Lui-senpai's cool, raspy, edgy vocals, so I chose this song.
超カッコよかったよね！
It was super cool, wasn't it?!
そして、6曲目が『星座になれたら』。さっきね、ふーちゃん達と一緒にワイワイした『星座になれたら』で、
And the 6th song was "If I Could Be a Constellation", the fun, lively version I just did with Fuu-chan and the gang,
7曲目、激エモのにゃんちゃん、おかゆ先輩との『打上花火』！
followed by the 7th song, a super emotional "Uchiage Hanabi" with Nyan-chan Okayu-senpai!
どうでしたか？本当に、おにぎりゃーの皆さんには申し訳ないんですけれども、
How was it? Honestly, to all the Onigiryaa, I'm really sorry,
あの瞬間はちょっと自分、おかゆ先輩の彼氏のつもりでもう...ってやってしまいました！
but in that moment, I kind of acted like I was Okayu-senpai's boyfriend!
もう最高でした。ありがとうございました、本当に！
It was absolutely the best. Thank you so much, really!
すいません、もうお返しします。すいません、ありがとうございました。
I'm sorry, I'll return her to you now. Sorry about that, and thank you so much!
というね、エモエモなパート、カッコいいからエモまでのパートがありましたが、楽しんでいただけてますかー？
So we had that super emotional part—from cool to emotional tracks—are you all enjoying it so far?
はーい！
Yay!
ちょっとコメント見てみようかな。
Let me take a look at the comments.
あ、「エモすぎた」「泣いた」。え、わかる！
Ah, "Too emotional", "I cried." Oh, I totally get it!
わかる！めっちゃエモいよね！
I know, right?! It was super emotional!
ちはもなんかやりながら、「エモすぎる、これ！」と思ってやってましたよー！
Even while performing, Chiha was thinking, "This is way too emotional!" Haha!
ありがとう！めっちゃ良かったよね！
Thank you! It was really great, wasn't it?!
さあ、ということでね、ちは喋らせると喋りすぎてしまうので、
Now then, if you let Chiha talk, I'll end up talking way too much,
次のパートに行きたいんですが、ここからは嬉しいお知らせとなります！
so I'd like to move on to the next part. From here, we have some exciting announcements!
イェーイ！
Yay!
輪堂千速 誕生日記念2026 グッズ販売の告知となります！
This is the announcement for Rindo Chihaya's Birthday Celebration 2026 Merchandise Sale!
生誕グッズが出るぞー！こちらをご覧ください！ドン！
Birthday merch is here! Please take a look at this! Ta-da!
はーい！盛りだくさんですねー！
Yes! There's a ton of stuff here!
イラストはトリダモノ先生ママに描いていただきましたー！ありがとうございます！
The illustration was drawn by Toridamono-sensei Mama! Thank you so much!
ギターを弾いてるライブのワンシーンをイメージして描いていただきました。いや、めっちゃカッコいいよね！
She drew it with the image of a live stage scene playing the guitar. Seriously, isn't it so cool?!
それではね、詳細を見ていきましょー！まずは、こちら！
Let's check out the details! First up, this one!
え、Chihaya BD Fes Tシャツ 2026 でございます！
The Chihaya BD Fes T-shirt 2026!
キービジュのイラスト全身を使用した、カッコ可愛いTシャツです！
It's a cool and cute T-shirt featuring the full-body key visual illustration!
バンドTシャツっぽくしたくてね、ちょっとロゴとかイカつい感じにしてもらったので、
I wanted it to feel like a band tee, so I had the logo and everything designed with a rugged vibe,
ぜひぜひ、ライブの時とか日常でも着てもらえたら嬉しいです！
so I'd be so happy if you wear it to concerts or even in your daily life!
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this!
ピックケースキーホルダーです！
The Pick Case Keychain!
お気に入りのピックを入れておしゃれに持ち運べるキーホルダーです。
It's a keychain where you can stylishly carry around your favorite guitar picks.
キーホルダーがメインで、3枚のピックは付属品としてついています。
The keychain is the main item, and it comes with three picks included.
ピックケースホルダーにはピックが1枚入る仕様です。
The pick case holder is designed to hold one pick.
今回のために書いたサインとかロゴとか、
It features the signature and logo drawn specifically for this occasion,
あとはタイトルにもなってる『FlatOut』のロゴが描かれてるピックがセットになっています。
and also the "FlatOut" logo—the title of this event—so a set of picks featuring that is included.
続いては、こちら！
Next up is this!
ちはとお出かけバッグです！
The "Going Out with Chiha" Bag!
前にポーチがついていて、前のポーチをひっくり返すと中身を見せて推しバッグにチェンジできる、
It has a pouch on the front, and when you flip the front pouch over, it shows what's inside and turns into a display bag!
機能性のある斜めがけのバッグになっています！
It's a super functional crossbody bag!
いろんなところ、これでお出かけしてください！
Please go out to all kinds of places with this!
そして、続いては、こちら！
And next up is this!
どこでもふぐ太郎ティッシュカバー！
The "Anywhere Fugutaro" Tissue Cover!
ふんわりとした質感の、ふぐ太郎モチーフのティッシュカバーです！
It's a soft, fluffy tissue cover with a Fugutaro motif!
え、可愛いよね！お家でも車でも職場でもふぐ太郎を連れていけます！
Isn't it so cute? You can take Fugutaro with you at home, in the car, or at work!
そして、続いては、こちら！
And next up is this!
シチュエーションボイスです！タイトルは『リハーサルボイス』！
A situation voice! The title is "Rehearsal Voice"!
ライブ前のリハーサルで、ドキドキ緊張してるちはのシチュエーションボイスになっておりますので、
It's a situation voice featuring a nervous Chiha with a racing heart during rehearsal right before the live,
ドキドキの緊張感をね、ぜひ聴きに来てください！
so please come listen to that thrilling, nervous feeling!
そして、フルセット購入特典もあります！こちら！
And there's also a Full Set Purchase Bonus! Here it is!
直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードです！
An instax-style bromide card with a handwritten signature & foil-stamped printed message!
全部ね、直筆でちはがサインを書きますのでね、ぜひぜひフルセットで購入していただけるととっても嬉しいです！
Chiha will be handwriting all the signatures by hand, so I'd be super happy if you get the full set!
そして特典ボイス、タイトルは『ライブ後、きみと』になります。
And the bonus voice is titled "With You, After the Live."
先ほどのボイスと合わせて聴くと、またよりエモさを感じられるのではないかなと思うので、
If you listen to it together with the previous voice, I think you'll feel even more emotion,
ぜひこちらも聴いてみてください！
so definitely give this one a listen too!
改めて、フルセットはこちらになります！
Once again, here is the full set!
これ全部、Tシャツ着てバッグ持ってキーホルダーつけて、ふぐ太郎を持って、
Wearing the T-shirt, holding the bag, attaching the keychain, holding Fugutaro...
どこでも行ける「ちはセット」となるので、ま、買うならフルセットの方がいいよね！
It's a "Chiha Set" that lets you go anywhere, so if you're buying, the full set is definitely the way to go!
この後21時カートオープンとなりますので、
The cart opens right after this at 9:00 PM,
数量限定ではないのでぜひね、ゆっくり購入していただけるととっても嬉しいです！
and it's not limited quantity, so please take your time and I'd be so happy if you purchase it!
お願いします！
Please check them out!
そして！皆様待望のお知らせが…ございます！
And! We have the long-awaited announcement!
こちら！
Look at this!
なんとー！輪堂千速ソロとして、初めてのオリ曲「Flatout」が
Surprise! Rindo Chihaya's very first solo original song, "Flatout"...
この後24時、7月9日木曜日の0時、この後ね、3時間ちょい後くらいからデジタルリリースされます！
...will be digitally released tonight at 24:00, July 9th midnight—in just a little over three hours!
やったー！
Yay!
こんなポーズしてる
I'm making this pose on the cover.
で、今回のライブのタイトルにもなっている「Flatout」は、オリ曲のタイトルでございました！
And "Flatout", the title of today's live concert, was actually the title of my original song!
えー、この配信が終わった後に、MVが公開されますので、そちらもぜひお楽しみに！
The music video will premiere right after this stream ends, so please look forward to it!
概要欄にね、あのーそのうち多分リンクが貼られたり貼られなかったりすると思うんでそちらもチェックしてみてください！
A link will probably be added to the description soon (or maybe not!), so be sure to check it out!
え、新曲、この後やっぱ早速聴きたいですよね！
Now, since it's a brand-new song, you want to hear it right away, don't you?
この後、披露するので絶対に聴いてください！
I'll be performing it right after this, so you definitely don't want to miss it!
最後まで！最後までね、チャンネルはそのままで見ていってくださいね！
Please keep your channel right here and watch until the very end, okay?
以上、輪堂千速生誕祭2026のグッズ情報と、リリース情報でしたー！
That concludes the merch and release info for Rindo Chihaya Birthday Fest 2026!
みんな買ってねー！サブスクでも聴いてねー！
Make sure to buy the merch, and stream the song too!
はい！ということで、怒涛のお知らせコーナーでした。
All right! That was our whirlwind announcements segment.
ここからいよいよライブもクライマックスです！でも、まだまだあります！
From here, the live concert is finally reaching its climax! But there's still plenty more to come!
盛り上がる準備できてますかー？最後一緒にブチ上げていこうねー！
Are you ready to get hyped? Let's turn up the heat together till the end!
では、準備してきます。
Well then, I'll go get ready.
あ、その…チャンネルはそのままで。
Ah, keep your channel right here.
[ワタリドリ / 作詞・作曲：川上洋平]
[Title: Wataridori / Lyrics & Music: Yohei Kawakami]
I wanna fly so high
Yeah, I know my wings are dry
「翼仰げば」って人は云う
People say, "Just look up at the wings,"
その向こうにあるは無情
but beyond them lies heartlessness.
飛べる者 落ちる者
Those who can fly, those who fall;
誰も見てない 気にも留めない
no one is watching, no one pays mind.
それでも飛び続けた
Even so, I kept flying on,
傷ついた言葉乗せ運びたいから
carrying wounded words, because I want to deliver them.
追いかけて届くよう
Chasing after them so they will reach,
僕等一心に羽ばたいて
we flap our wings with all our might.
問いかけて嘆いた夜
On the night we questioned and grieved,
故郷は一層輝いて
our hometown shone even brighter.
ワタリドリの様に今旅に発つよ
Like migratory birds, we depart on our journey now,
ありもしないストーリーを
and an impossible story,
描いてみせるよ
I'll show you I can paint it!
I wanna fly so far away with my guitar
「一人じゃない」って人々は歌う
People sing, "You're not alone,"
間違いじゃない 理想論でもない
it's not wrong, nor is it mere idealism,
ただ頼って生きたくはない
I just don't want to live relying on others.
誰も聴いていない 気にも留めない
No one is listening, no one pays mind,
それでも歌い続けた
even so, I kept on singing,
傷ついたあなたを笑わせたいから
because I want to make you smile when you're hurt.
追い風届けるよ
I'll send a tailwind your way,
僕等一心に羽ばたいて
as we flap our wings with all our might.
遠い過去を背負ってた
You, burdened with a distant past—
あなたを未来へ運ぶよ
I will carry you into the future.
ワタリドリの様に今 群れをなして
Like migratory birds, forming a flock now,
大それた四重奏を奏で終える日まで
until the day we finish playing this audacious quartet!
All this time we come and we grow
Now it's time that we should go
But we both know that this is for sure
It's not the end of the world
Well, see you one day
追いかけて届くよう
Chasing after them so they will reach,
僕等一心に羽ばたいて
we flap our wings with all our might.
問いかけて嘆いた夜
On the night we questioned and grieved,
朝焼け色に染まっていく
it's getting dyed in the colors of the dawn.
ワタリドリの様にいつか舞い戻るよ
Like migratory birds, we'll fly back someday,
ありもしないストーリーを
to an impossible story,
いつかまた会う日まで
until the day we meet again!
Shiny Smily Story (2022 ver.)
作詞：金丸佳史 作曲：中野領太 編曲：秋浦智裕
Lyrics: Yoshifumi Kanamaru / Music: Ryota Nakano / Arrangement: Tomohiro Akiura
はい、ということで！
All right, with that said!
輪堂千速生誕祭、ここまで見てくれたみんな、本当にありがとうございます！
To everyone who watched Rindou Chihaya's Birthday Festival up to this point, thank you so very much!
えー、次が本当にラストの曲です。
Um, next is truly the final song.
えー、この曲は、いつかみんなと現地で会って、ライブができたときに、
Um, this is a song that, when I'm someday able to meet everyone in person and do a live concert,
最後に歌えたらいいなって、そんな思いで千速のいろんな気持ちを込めて作ってもらった曲です。
I hoped I could sing at the very end, so it was created pouring all of Chihaya's various feelings into it.
千速の、初めてのオリ曲、聴いてください。『Flat out』。
Please listen to Chihaya's very first original song: "Flat out."
メランコリーのリフレイン 午前三時
A melancholy refrain at 3:00 AM,
夢を見るには少し遅すぎた Midnight
Midnight, a bit too late to be dreaming.
言葉にならないままの想いが
Unspoken feelings that couldn't find words—
溢れだしてしまう前に
before they spill over,
飛び出した部屋 光を見たくて
I dashed out of my room, longing to see the light.
“どうせ”“だって”何度だって諦めようとしたって
"No point," "Because"—no matter how many times I tried to give up,
“だけど”“きっと”今日もそっと伸ばした手 あの星まで
"Yet," "Surely"—today too, I gently reached out my hand toward that star.
自分さえだませない 嘘はもうやめて
Stop lying, unable to deceive even yourself,
踏み込め
and step forward!
駆け抜けて 音も風も抜き去って
Dash through, leaving both sound and wind behind!
迷いさえも振り切って スピードを上げて
Shaking off all hesitation, pick up the speed!
行かなくちゃ 夜のまだその向こうへ
I have to go, far beyond this night,
見たこともない世界へ 今最高速度で 高鳴る方へ
to a world I've never seen, now at top speed, toward what makes my heart race!
答えなんてなくたって ただこうしていたいだけ
Even without an answer, I just want to stay like this.
未完成で不完全な道の先まで
To the end of this unfinished, imperfect road,
行ける 信じて
I can make it—believe in it!
差し障りないように生きた日々
The days I lived just avoiding any trouble...
諦めの言い訳を探すの止めて
I stopped searching for excuses to give up.
もどかしい気持ち 窓の向こうに
With this frustrating feeling, beyond the window,
輝くあの星みたいになりたかったんだ
I always wanted to become like that shining star.
足りない物だらけだって
Even if I'm full of shortcomings,
どれだけ離されたって 止まればそこまでなんだ
no matter how far behind I am, if I stop, that's where it ends!
進め 進め
Keep moving forward! Keep moving forward!
未来を変える瞬間は いつかじゃなくて今なんだ
The moment to change the future isn't "someday"—it's right now!
進め 進め 先へ
Keep moving forward! Keep moving forward, further ahead!
もっと遠くまで
Even further away...
確かめに行くんだ Flat out
I'm going to make sure, flat out!
駆け抜けて 夢に見たその舞台へ
Dash through, toward the stage I dreamed of!
決して振り返らないで スピードをあげて
Never look back, pick up the speed!
行かなくちゃ 夜のまだその向こうへ
I have to go, far beyond this night,
見たこともない世界へ 今最高速度で 信じる方へ
to a world I've never seen, now at top speed, toward what I believe in!
答えなんてなくたって ただこうして走り出したんだ
Even without an answer, I just started running like this.
止まらないよ さあ あの星に届け
I won't stop—come on, reach that star!
輪堂千速生誕祭2026、見ていただいて本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you all so very much for watching the Rindou Chihaya Birthday Festival 2026!
これからも、みんなと向こう側の景色たくさん見に行きたいです！
From here on, I want to go see so many views on the other side together with everyone!
これからも千速のことを好きでいてついてきてくれたら嬉しいです！
I'd be so happy if you keep loving Chihaya and staying by my side!
本当に今日はありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much for today!
ありがとねー！
Thank you!
輪堂千速生誕LIVE お越しいただきありがとうございます 初めてのライブはどうでしたか？？
[Rindou Chihaya Birthday LIVE: Thank you so much for coming. How was my first live concert??]
見てくれたキミがいて初めてLIVE完成します いつかキミの声が直接きけるその時まで
[This LIVE is only complete because you were here watching. Until the day I can hear your voice in person,]
これからも走り続けるよ！！ 今日は本当にありがとう
[I'll keep on running!! Thank you so much for today.]
輪堂千早生誕LIVE
[Chihaya Rindo Birthday Live]
お越しいただきありがとうございます
Thank you so much for coming!
初めてのライブはどうでしたか？？
How was my first live concert??
見てくれたキミがいて初めて完成します
It is only complete because you were here to watch it.
いつかキミの声が直接きけるその時まで
Until the day I can hear your voices in person,
これからも走り続けるよ！！
I'll keep on running!!
今日は本当にありがとう
Thank you so much for today!